- Oh, good, your power's out too.
- Why is that good?
(Penny:)Last month, I sent the electric company
a Starbucks gift card...
(Penny:)...an apology note
and a few snapshots of me in a bra.
(Sheldon:)Power failure.
Implementing power-failure protocol.
(Leonard:)What happened to all your glow-in-the-dark
emergency-exit stuff painted on the floor?
(Sheldon:)Oh, that was wildly carcinogenic.
Anyway, too bad you're no longer entitled
to the full benefits of my friendship...
(Sheldon:)...because I happen to be
extremely prepared for such an emergency.
(Sheldon:)Please try not to see anything
by this light.
(Sheldon:)It's not for you.
It's a blackout,
I'm sure the power will be back on soon.
(Sheldon:)And I'm sure some fool in the Donner Party
said the snow would stop any day now.
(Sheldon:)I like to think they ate him first.
I got candles in my apartment.
(Sheldon:)Candles? During a blackout?
Are you mad? That's a fire hazard.
(Sheldon:)No, Pasadena Water and Power
recommends the far safer glow stick.